Guide to the Records of the Vice President and Deputy Chancellor and Senior Vice President, Debra James 1980-2000 RG.6.1.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Topical Files
  - C. Duncan Rice, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Mike Robins, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Jose Rivera--University of Sacred Heart, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - St. Peter's College, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Sales Order, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Salmungundi, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Minutes of SSC Meetings, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - John O'Connor, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226356 9
  - Board Senate and Letter to Community, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Vincent D. Dominico, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Glenda Doyle, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - H.L. Gates, Jr., undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Commencement, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Items Sent to Trish, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Jay Talk to Me, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Medical Commencement, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Speech Ideas/Concepts, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Stern School of Business Pre-Commencement Exercises, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Coleen, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - To Read, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - FAS Search Committee, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226363 5
  - FAS, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - FAS, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Professor Susan Carey, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - FAS, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - FAS Rutgers University, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Faulker and Gray, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Financial Advisory Comm. Meeting, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Founders' Day, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Founders' Day, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Founders' Day, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Founders' Day, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Founders' Day, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Flowers, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - First Lady of Lebanon, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Fire Safety Handbook, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Financial Aid Advisor Committee, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Financial Aid, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Financial Aid, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - 4 Way, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - 4 Way, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - 4 Way, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - 4 Way Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Friends of Wagner College, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Governor's Island, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Liaison Officer Correspondence About the L.O. Meeting, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Resource Network, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Members of the All-university Selection Committee--Distinguished Administrator Award, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Dean's Meeting, Oct 5, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Meeting, Oct 12, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Meeting, Aug 24, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Meeting, Aug 31, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Meeting, Sep 7, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Dean's Meeting, Jan 18, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Dean's Meeting, Feb 1, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Meeting, Feb 8, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Dean's Meeting, Feb 15, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 1, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 15, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 22, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 23, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Dean's Meeting, Apr 5, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Meeting, Apr 12, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Meeting, Apr 19, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Dean's Meeting, May 3, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Dean's Meeting, May 10, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Meeting, May 24, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Meeting, Jun 14, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Dean's Meeting, Jul 12, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Dean's Meeting, Aug 30, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Meeting, Sep 13, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Dean's Meeting, Sep 6, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Dean's Meeting, Oct 4, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Dean's Meeting, Oct 11, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Dean's Meeting, Oct 18, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Dean's Meeting, Nov 1, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Dean's Meeting, Nov 8, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Dean's Meeting, Nov 15, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Dean's Meeting, Nov 22, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Dean's Meeting, Dec 6, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Dean's Meeting, Dec 13, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Dean's Meeting, Jan 10, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Dean's Meeting, Jan 17, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Dean's Meeting, Jan 24, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Dean's Meeting, Feb 7, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Dean's Meeting, Feb 14, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Dean's Meeting, Feb 21, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 7, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 14, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Dean's Meeting, Mar 21, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Dean's Meeting, Apr 4, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Dean's Meeting, Apr 11, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Dean's Meeting, Apr 18, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Dean's Meeting, May 2, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Dean's Meeting, May 9, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Dean's Meeting, May 23, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 48)